
#Quiz_Data holds most of the data for the quiz app. It is storing all the questions, choices, and answers.
quiz_data = [  
    {
        "question": "From largest to smallest, what are the categories for naming an organism?",
        "choices": [
            "Phylum, Order, Family, Genus, Species, Kingdom, Class",
            "Kingdom, Phylum, Class, Order, Family, Genus, Species",
            "Species, Genus, Order, Class, Phylum, Order, Kingdom",
            "Kingdom, Phylum, Class, Order, Family, Species, Genus"
        ],
        "answers": "Kingdom, Phylum, Class, Order, Family, Genus, Species"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who came up with a system of taxonomic organization?",
        "choices": [
            "Charles Darwin", "James Watson", "Carl Linnaeus", "Gregor Mendel"
        ],
        "answers": "Carl Linnaeus"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the animal's way of maintaining internal conditions in a changing environment.",
        "choices": [
            "Conditioning", "Homeostasis", "Taxonomy", "Regulation"
        ],
        "answers": "Homeostasis"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Scientific name of an organism consists of...",
        "choices": [
            "Kingdom Genus", "Genus Species", "Kingdom Phylum", "Class Species"
        ],
        "answers": "Genus Species"
    },
    {
        "question": "The process by which two monomers are linked is calledâ€¦",
        "choices": [
            "Dehydration Synthesis", "Hydrolysis", "Dehydration Hydrolysis", "Polymer Synthesis"
        ],
        "answers": "Dehydration Synthesis"
    },
    {
        "question": "Proteins are a diverse group of molecules. There are twenty _____ that makes up all proteins, in different numbers and combinations.",
        "choices": [
            "Nucleotides", "Monomers", "Amino Acids", "Carbohydrates"
        ],
        "answers": "Amino Acids"
    },
    {
        "question": "The pH of blood is between 7.35 and 7.45 making it...",
        "choices": [
            "Neutral", "Slightly Acidic", "Slightly Basic", "Very Acidic"
        ],
        "answers": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "The monomers are nucleotides that form polymers like:",
        "choices": [
            "DNA (Genes)", "RNA (Protein Synthesis)", "ATP (Energy for Cellular Work)", "All of the above"
        ],
        "answers": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "The word 'aerobic' means: ",
        "choices": [
            "With ATP", "With Oxygen", "Without Oxygen", "With Carbon Dioxide"
        ],
        "answers": "With Oxygen"
    },
    {
        "question": "An enzyme is _______.",
        "choices": [
            "a protein", "a lipid.", "a carbohydrates.", "an amino acid."
        ],
        "answers": "a protein"
    },
    {
        "question": "This organelle is the 'powerhouse of the cell' and is the main site for cellular respiration.",
        "choices": [
            "Nucleus", "Lyson", "Mitochondria", "Golgi Apparatus"
        ],
        "answers": "Mitochondria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Only some of the energy of cellular respiration is the formation of ATP. The rest is released as _____.",
        "choices": [
            "ATP", "Heat", "Fuel Molecules", "Carbon Dioxide"
        ],
        "answers": "Heat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a part of the cytoskeleton (internal framework) of a cell?",
        "choices": [
            "Cilia", "Intermediate Filaments", "Mitotubules", "Microfilaments"
        ],
        "answers": "Cilia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What organelle is responsible for the modifying and packaging of proteins?",
        "choices": [
            "Lysosomes", "Mitochondria", "Golgi Apparatus", "Nucleus"
        ],
        "answers": "Golgi Apparatus"
    },
    {
        "question": "A cuttlefish can change color due to pigment changes in the ____ cells.",
        "choices": [
            "Algae", "Chromatophore", "Nematocyst", "Cnidocyte"
        ],
        "answers": "Chromatophore"
    },
    {
        "question": "All eukaryotic cells have three basic parts they are which of the following?",
        "choices": [
            "The nucleus, cytoskeleton, and mitochondria", "The nucleus, cytoskeleton, and mitochondria", "The plasma membrane, cytoplasm, and nucleus", "The plasma membrane, cytoplasm, and nucleus"
        ],
        "answers": "The plasma membrane, cytoplasm, and nucleus"
    },
    {
        "question": "All organisms are made of cells. Cells are the basic units of life. This statement is also referred to as: ",
        "choices": [
            "National Selection", "Inheritance", "Cell Theory", "The Cell Hypothesis"
        ],
        "answers": "Cell Theory"
    }
]

